Hello.
So there's one more thing we need to do to finish designing our level, and that is to place the enemies
and the items that we've made in the previous lectures.
First, I'm going to place my enemies around my map, so I'm going to go to my scan folder and dragging
my scan to blueprint.
And make sure to put them in the same layer as our player character.
So for me, it's layer 20 and the Y axis.
And I'm going to place a couple skeletons around my map.
So I think updates from there and another one here.
And also one here.
And then finally, I'm going to play some mushroom enemies.
So I'm going to place one towards the end of the level here.
I'll move it to layer 20.
And let's just rotate them so they're facing the opposite direction.
So I can go here, select and rotate, and let's rotate them 180 degrees.
Let's also add a mushroom enemy.
Over here.
Okay.
I've added a lot of enemies, so let's add some health pickups in my level.
So I'll move this to 20 and.
We can add one here.
And we can add another one here.
And I'll add one final one here.
Okay, let's add some coins along our level.
By the way, a quick way to duplicate things inside an unreal engine is to select the object you want
to duplicate and then hold the open and then move it, and then that will quickly duplicate it.
So I'm going to do that to move some coins around my level.
Next, I'm going to add some checkpoints to my level.
So I'm going to add one here.
I'm only going to have one checkpoint.
And finally, let's add some spikes so we can add a spike here.
So I only have one spike and one checkpoint, but this is just to showcase me adding the different items.
And now let's go play and test out our level.
I can go play.
I made the first bit empty.
Then we have some cool coins to collect.
There's a skeleton over here.
I can attack him.
But I'm going to ask you a boy.
Don't.
I'll jump over him.
I can get this hot, but I feel out I work.
Oh, one more thing I've got to do to my level.
If we select it and go to search and look for tag and give this the tag of war, that way we'll be able
to walk slide on the walls of this level.
Ask a play and I'll quickly speed through to get to the bit I was at.
So I should be able to water it so I can water it in my level.
Nice.
Hello.
As I was playing my game, I noticed a couple of issues.
So the first one is the enemy's projectiles.
And also my projectiles don't have collision with the world.
The second issue is my player character no longer has a screen check effect when they become damaged.
And the third issue is with my scan as an enemy, it can still attack me even when it dies.
So let me kill my skeleton.
So as I scanned, it can come back and still attack me.
So we need to fix all those issues.